Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES VI: MINUTES - GENERAL MEETINGS, 1882-1974 (Box-folder 15/1-18/25)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1933 - December 1933 (Box-folder 16/40)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, Jan 1934 - June 1934 (Box-folder 16/41)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1934 - December 1934 (Box-folder 16/42)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, Jan 1935 - June 1935 (Box-folder 16/43)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1935 - December 1935 (Box-folder 16/44)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,Jan 1936 - June 1936 (Box-folder 16/45)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1936 - December 1936 (Box-folder 16/46)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, Jan 1946 - June 1946 (Box-folder 16/47)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1946 - December 1946 (Box-folder 16/48)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, Jan 1947 - June 1947 (Box-folder 16/49)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,July 1947 - December 1947 (Box-folder 16/50)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1948-June 1948 (Box-folder 16/51)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1948 - December 1948 (Box-folder 16/52)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1949-June 1949 (Box-folder 16/53)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1949 - December 1949 (Box-folder 16/54)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1950-June 1950 (Box-folder 16/55)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1950 - December 1950 (Box-folder 16/56)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1951-June 1951 (Box-folder 16/57)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1951 - December 1951 (Box-folder 16/58)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1952-June 1952 (Box-folder 16/59)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1952 - December 1952 (Box-folder 16/60)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1953-June 1953 (Box-folder 16/61)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1953 - December 1953 (Box-folder 16/62)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1954-June 1954 (Box-folder 16/63)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1954-December 1954 (Box-folder 16/64)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1955-June 1955 (Box-folder 16/65)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1955-December 1955 (Box-folder 16/66)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1956-June 1956 (Box-folder 16/67)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1957-December 1957, 1956 (Box-folder 16/68)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1957-June 1957 (Box-folder 16/69)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July 1958-December 1958, 1957 (Box-folder 16/70)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1958-June 1958 (Box-folder 16/71)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1958 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1959 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, July-December 1959 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1960 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1960 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-April 1961 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May-August 1961 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, September-December 1961 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-March 1962 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, April-June 1962 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-October 1962 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, November-December 1962 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-April 1963 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May-July 1963 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, August-September 1963 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, October-December 1963 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-March 1964 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, April-June 1964 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, July-October 1964 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, November-December 1964 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-April 1965 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May-September 1965 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, October-December 1965 (Box-folder 17/23)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-April 1966 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May-August 1966 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, September 1966-December 1966 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1967-April 1967 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1967-September 1967 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, October 1967-December 1967 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1968-April 1968 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1968-September 1968 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, October 1968-December 1968 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, January 1969-April 1969 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1969-September 1969 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, October 1969-December 1969 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1970-April 1970 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, May 1970-August 1970 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, September 1970-December 1970 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1971-March 1971 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, April 1971-July 1971 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, August 1971-October 1971 (Box-folder 18/16)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, November 1971-December 1971 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1972-April 1972 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, May 1972-August 1972 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, September 1972-December 1972 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1973-March 1973 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,, April 1973-July 1973 (Box-folder 18/22)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, August 1973-December 1973 (Box-folder 18/23)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January 1974-March 1974 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, April 1974-May 1974 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - SERIES VII: MINUTES - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1907-1974 (Box-folder 19/1-19/101)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, June 1907-December 1908, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1909 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1909 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1910 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1911 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1912 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1913 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1914 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1915 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1916 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1917 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1918 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1919 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1920 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1921 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1922 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1923 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1924 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1925 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1926 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1927 (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1928 (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1929 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1930 (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1931 (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1934 (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, 1936 (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1938 (Box-folder 19/29)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1938 (Box-folder 19/30)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1939 (Box-folder 19/31)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1939 (Box-folder 19/32)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1940 (Box-folder 19/33)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1940 (Box-folder 19/34)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1941 (Box-folder 19/35)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1941 (Box-folder 19/36)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1942 (Box-folder 19/37)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1942 (Box-folder 19/38)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1943 (Box-folder 19/39)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1943 (Box-folder 19/40)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1944 (Box-folder 19/41)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1944 (Box-folder 19/42)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1945 (Box-folder 19/43)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1945 (Box-folder 19/44)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1946 (Box-folder 19/45)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1946 (Box-folder 19/46)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1947 (Box-folder 19/47)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1947 (Box-folder 19/48)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1948 (Box-folder 19/49)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1948 (Box-folder 19/50)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1949 (Box-folder 19/51)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1949 (Box-folder 19/52)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,January-June 1950 (Box-folder 19/53)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1950 (Box-folder 19/54)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1951 (Box-folder 19/55)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1951 (Box-folder 19/56)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, Jan-June 1952 (Box-folder 19/57)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1952 (Box-folder 19/58)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1953 (Box-folder 19/59)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1953 (Box-folder 19/60)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1954 (Box-folder 19/61)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December1954 (Box-folder 19/62)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,January-June 1955 (Box-folder 19/63)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1955 (Box-folder 19/64)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1956 (Box-folder 19/65)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1956 (Box-folder 19/66)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1957 (Box-folder 19/67)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1957 (Box-folder 19/68)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1958 (Box-folder 19/69)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1958 (Box-folder 19/70)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1959 (Box-folder 19/71)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1959 (Box-folder 19/72)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1960 (Box-folder 19/73)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes,July-December 1960 (Box-folder 19/74)